Hello everyone, I am Stella from Cloud Shanghai.
Today, I and my colleague Familia will introduce the new features of version 7.1.
This time, our new features are divided into 8 parts.
These are the main updates, 3D function, 2D function, virtual model, process details, rendering, text editor and other files.
Now let's take a look at the main update content.
The first update content is the seamless text editor.
This update has added the seamless text editor.
You can use the scanned image to generate continuous text in all directions.
You can also check the effect in the 3D window.
There are two modes, automatic mode and manual mode.
Next, let's learn how to use this function.
First, let's go to the object window.
Let's go to the object window.
Find the object.
On the right side, you can see that a plus button has been added.
We will stop the mouse on the top.
You can see that the seamless text editor is created.
Open the text editor.
The window of the text editor will appear in the 2D window.
Next, I will introduce the structure of the text editor window.
First, it is divided into two windows.
The upper part is the editing window of the object text area.
The lower part is the preview window of the result.
We will press the button at the bottom left to open the original text.
You can see the original text image in the top editing window.
The scroll wheel can be placed in the size of the text.
At the top, you can see the size and resolution of the sample.
The maximum size that can be supported at the moment is 9999 pixels multiplied by 9999 pixels.
If the original image is larger than this value, it will be automatically lowered to 9999.
So please make sure that the size of the original image is smaller than the upper limit value.
We can see the material ball on the upper left.
Click to switch to check.
Because this image has been created before loading,
the system will automatically detect the found image and import it.
This is the secret rule of the picture.
Pictures that need to be imported together must use the same name as the original text.
In addition, the system can detect these pictures only by using the English downward line and the corresponding backslash.
For example, the backslash of the found image is because of the downward line Normal or the downward line NRM.
The other material pictures are the same.
Next, let's introduce the automatic mode.
Let's introduce the automatic mode.
First, select the physical area.
We find the smallest area where the tree pattern repeats.
When choosing, it should be larger than this area.
Then press the left mouse button to drag and select.
The selected area is recommended to be larger than 200x200 pixels.
After the selection is complete, these small blue grid will appear within the frame selection range.
This is the single cycle range selected after automatic analysis.
In the window below, it will display the results of the automatic analysis of the selected area.
The scroll mouse wheel can enlarge and shrink the tree pattern.
When you open the grid button in the window, you can identify the original location of the area through the line.
You can check the clothing effect in the 3D window.
For example, if you want to adjust the area, you can drag and select again.
Or move to select the point of the area.
After adjustment, you will automatically analyze and generate the results in the selected area again.
In the lower right corner of the selected area, you can see the icon of the automatic mode.
You can see the automatic mode description on the top of the icon.
The selected area will automatically adjust to the best result.
In the automatic mode, you can set the right upper corner of the tree type and the average option.
Choosing the tree type is to get a more accurate analysis result.
And because the tree type is based on the line chart,
Therefore, it still needs to be in the line chart.
It needs to be in the line chart in order to generate the result.
You can see that the small triangle of the tree type has pure color, duplicate and random.
Pure color refers to the pure color of the tree without a pattern.
Duplicate refers to the tree pattern with a rule.
Random refers to the tree pattern without a rule.
Adjusting the average value can be used to average the difference in brightness caused by the fold marks caused by the tree.
The button on the far right is the smooth button.
If the original image is not scanned evenly,
Or the link part of the repeated image is not smooth due to the fold marks,
The automatic adjustment result may not be very good.
In this case, opening the smooth can evenly match the image.
You can see that the image we just drew has some uneven areas.
We open the smooth and the image is evenly matched.
After introducing the automatic mode,
Now let's introduce the manual mode.
I'm going to open a grid material now.
When the part of the repetition of the text is relatively clear,
You can also use the manual mode when choosing the text area.
This is the single-circle size of our frame selection.
It's similar to the peek-and-seek function in PS.
The left-click drags the frame to select the smallest circle of this pattern.
It is still in the automatic mode.
Because the automatic mode is the default mode.
You can click the button at the bottom right of the selected area.
Change the mode to manual mode to keep the selected area.
The manual mode is a small hand-shaped icon.
After switching to manual mode,
You need to re-adjust the selected area.
The preview window at the bottom will update the new selection range.
And generate four consecutive repetition effects.
If you look at the preview effect at the bottom,
It doesn't feel ideal.
You can continue to adjust the area.
Let's move to the selected area to adjust it closely.
After the selection is complete,
It also generates four consecutive repetition effects in the preview window.
After editing the text,
We can click the save button at the bottom to save.
If it matches the multiple text,
You can click on the selection in the preview window.
You can save multiple text at a time.
Then click OK.
After the selection is complete,
You can confirm it.
You can enter the name of the file.
Click save.
If you want to use the completed image for the object,
And use it immediately,
You can click on the application at the bottom and close it.
The texture will be applied to the object that was selected at the beginning.
And the texture generator will be turned off at the same time.
Before that,
We need to use other software to generate a seamless texture.
Now you can easily generate a seamless texture in Cloud.
Next, I will introduce another optimization for you.
In the new version of 7.1,
We added automatic 3D arrangement.
It can help us to arrange the panels around the model quickly.
First, we have already added a virtual model.
Now we will add a single size.
In order to arrange the accuracy of the calculation,
We need to set the panel to a symmetrical state.
Now we will set the panel to a symmetrical state.
After setting it up,
In the 3D window tool bar,
In the lower left corner,
We will find the automatic 3D arrangement button.
Click on it,
A dynamic frame will pop up.
The panel will be arranged in 3D according to the accuracy.
This function is based on the result of learning from a large number of panel data.
In addition to using the 3D tool,
It can also be used to make the panel 3D.
It is useful for more accurate arrangement.
Let's click on the operation.
The panel will start to arrange automatically.
The panel arranged in each step
Is divided by color and transparency.
If you want to check the arrangement results of each step,
You can press the back and forth button
And the next step button.
Click to confirm the automatic arrangement.
Turn it over and see if the arrangement position is correct.
As you can see,
The arrangement position of the panel in the back of the arm is not correct.
So after the automatic arrangement is finished,
You can also manually arrange the panel.
Open the arrangement point
Arrange the panel at the appropriate position.
and arrange them in the right place.
Next, I will introduce the new function,
which is automatically converted to action.
This function can convert the action file on the external platform
to the action file of Cloud.
First, select the virtual model in the main menu on the top,
and select automatically convert to action.
Then, we will enter the animation mode.
In the window that pops out,
you can select the gender of the module that needs to be converted.
Then, click on the file folder button at the bottom,
and open the FBX file that has been downloaded.
Note that the path name must remain in full English.
Then click convert.
After the conversion is successful,
you will see this pop-up window.
You can click save at this time,
and you can also close it first.
First, play the preview in the animation mode.
After confirming that there is no error,
you can save the file as a link to the action.
The default saved path is under the virtual model file in the library.
The file format of the action file is mpn.
Name this file as work,
and then save.
Click confirm.
And in 7.1,
all the action and posture files can be integrated into all the Cloud models.
Now let's open a model.
Then double-click.
Double-click to select the action file in the mpn format that has just been saved.
Then click confirm.
Play the action effect.
Click confirm.
Double-click to select the action file in the mpn format that has just been saved.
Similarly, the posture file can also be integrated.
Now let's go back to the simulation mode.
First, open a model.
Then open the virtual model file in the library window.
Open the male model v2 file folder.
Open the posture.
Use this male model v207 pose as an example.
The male model posture can be integrated into the female model.
Click confirm.
The virtual model editor has also improved significantly this time.
Now we have opened a virtual model.
Then click the virtual model editor in the upper left corner of the menu bar.
The virtual model editor.
You can see that the window of the virtual model editor is now in the position of the 2D window.
It can be conveniently switched to the 2D window.
The improved interface can also be more convenient to adjust the model's body shape.
It will be more friendly in operation.
There are now three versions of the model editor.
Full body.
Body shape and details.
Compared to the previous version, the body shape version has been added.
And optimized the UI interface of the detail panel.
Compared to the previous interface.
The upper body.
The lower body.
And other data are categorized.
These data are more intuitive.
Clear and clear.
Easy to edit and operate.
At the top.
You can change the preset size of different standards.
The right side.
At the top.
You can change the preset size of different standards.
The document here.
It is the size document of the virtual model in our virtual window.
Now you can go directly to this side to make a change and look.
The three buttons at the back are reset, open, and save.
Click the reset button to return to default size.
In the full body section, this update increases the weight option in the width column.
By entering the model's weight data, we can see the model's body shape change very objectively.
For example, we will change 50 kg to 60 kg.
After entering the weight, you can choose different body shapes at the bottom to adjust the different body shapes.
The male and female models can be changed here.
The male model cannot be changed.
This weight and body shape update is more suitable for such use scenarios.
When you don't know the exact body shape data, you only know the height and weight.
Knowing the approximate body shape, using this mode can quickly create a virtual model that is closer to the real human body.
In the details section, in addition to the original basic and advanced options,
we added the simple option.
When we select the weight in the width column,
it will automatically switch to the simple option.
If you know the model's three-dimensional data, you can also enter it here.
Other data that has not been entered can be automatically calculated.
It should be noted that the simple mode is a combination of the width and the weight.
And only when choosing the simple option can you choose the model's body shape.
The human body data below the change body shape will change accordingly.
Click on the button on the right to see all the size data.
Gray data cannot be edited in the current details box.
In order to see the model more conveniently,
we will start from the 7.1 version.
The model will be changed from the mode to the editor window.
No need to change the mode.
You can easily see it.
Before we see the model, we need to simulate the clothing of each size.
The original 7.1,
the model is in the model mode in the upper right corner.
After opening it, it will occupy the window of the whole picture.
Now it is located in the main menu column editor to see the model.
Click on the window where the model editor will appear.
You can compare the clothing of different sizes in the same picture.
With the window parallel to the 2D window,
you can see more directly.
Adjust the image of the version.
In the lower left corner,
you can switch to the 3D window.
The tool bar is horizontal.
Now the tool bar is vertical.
If we adjust the information of the version,
for example, adjust the total size,
increase to 100 mm.
Click on the update button in the upper left corner of the small window.
You can see the effect of the actual update of the number of numbers.
If you want to update all the numbers at once,
you can click on the big update button in the tool bar on the left.
It is more convenient to see the actual change of the clothing of all the numbers.
If you want three numbers to stand in a row,
we can make the 3D window a little bigger.
Because the default system is the automatic layout.
Due to the limitation of the window size,
Elma will automatically switch to the second row.
When saving the picture,
if you need the effect of a row,
remember to make the window larger,
and let the model line up into a row.
Or choose the row level and then save.
Because this picture is saved in the state displayed by the current window.
Next, I will introduce you to the improvement of the zipper.
In order to show a more realistic zipper,
this update has added the OBJ zipper function.
First of all, we have now opened a clothing file.
Here we have the 3D zipper that we added in advance.
After selecting the zipper,
you can see that the zipper type has been increased.
The default type is fabric.
Click on the triangle to select the OBJ type.
We will convert the zipper to OBJ zipper.
There are also six types of preset types.
There are paper, metal, nylon, and invisible zipper.
We can now switch to different types
to see the effect of OBJ zipper.
Finally, let's choose a metal.
Then in the material type of zipper,
select metal,
and modify its metal preset.
Now the OBJ zipper can be applied to different materials.
Let's take this zipper as an example.
This is the OBJ zipper that I added in advance.
We select the zipper in the 3D window.
At this time, we have the same zipper and also the top and bottomize.
We can see that the top and top are also highlighted in yellow.
We need to click here to see it.
At this time, we selected the zipper.
Click here to see it again.
We now select the bottom of the zipper.
The bottom of the zipper has been selected.
We will modify the material into a quantity in the attribute editor.
We can also modify its color.
We will use the same operation to select the upper part of the pull chain.
In the attribute editor, we will modify the material into metal.
We can also read the original OBJ's text, information and color information.
To make it easier to manage the components,
7.1 added a component column in the object window.
We will use the built-in pattern to explain the component column.
Let's use this built-in pattern as an example to explain the component column.
First, let's go to the object window.
You can see a small butterfly icon.
Click on the small butterfly icon.
You can see the component added to this built-in pattern.
This component is the eight-word button and the ring button.
You can also see the component in the previous scene column.
Let's click on the scene.
Now that we have made the component column separately,
we can manage this type of component.
You can see four components in the scene.
But in fact, it is a two-type component.
The eight-word button and the ring button.
So there are two components in one type.
Now the separate component column can better manage the components.
Let's go back to the component column.
For example, we have added a lot of similar components to the clothing.
If you want to modify the color and material,
you can only modify them one by one.
Now that there is a component,
you can directly select the component in the component column and modify it one by one.
And we can see the structure and component information of this component in the attribute editor.
You can edit it and enter it.
In the material list editor,
the component is also added.
Here you can calculate its material cost.
It is more convenient to manage the cost of clothing.
In this update,
the clothing roll function is added.
It is convenient to help us.
It helps us to make some clothes,
sleeves,
collar,
and other clothing parts.
When you see this clothing document,
for example,
we want to roll up this sleeve.
Before that,
we usually use the addition of the internal line.
Then use the folding arrangement tool to operate.
And it is difficult to make the effect of rolling two to three times.
Now we have this folding function.
We can quickly make the effect of rolling we want.
Let's take a look at the thickness and thickness of the chest of the sleeve and the thickness of the chest of the sleeve.
In the attribute editor,
you can see that it is default 20 and 2.5.
Then use the edit sheet tool.
Click on the outside line of the roll,
and then right-click.
If the position of the roll is made up of multiple sheets,
press the Shift key to select multiple edges,
and then right-click.
Select the roll in the menu bar.
Enter the number and distance of the roll you want to roll.
Set the number to 2 times.
Here the maximum roll number is 3 times.
We set the distance to 35 mm,
and then click OK.
You can see that the sleeve of the roll in the 3D window has been rolled up.
At this time,
the thickness of the chest of the sleeve and the thickness of the chest of the chest of the chest of the sleeve has become 10 and 4.
This change is to be able to simulate the effect of rolling more firmly and steadily.
We can continue to reduce these two values according to the effect.
Let's move on to the next step.
Roll the sleeve and adjust the surface of the sleeve!
After they are rolled up,
we'll delete the other side of the sleeve.
Just copy and match it directly,
then simulate again.
The above are the main functions of the explanation.
Next, I will introduce the updates of the 3D function.
The first one is the optimization of the 3D shape line tool.
You can edit by size.
The second one is the optimization of the performance of the 3D sewing line.
First, let's take a look at the shape line.
Press the size to edit.
Previously, when using the 3D shape line tool,
we can only modify the version by feeling.
But now we can directly enter the value by right-clicking,
and make the correct changes.
For example, let's use this style as an example.
First, we choose the tool to edit the shape line.
Then click on the tool to activate the costume.
For example, we want this princess line to move 15 mm outward.
Select this point and drag it to the right.
At the same time as dragging,
a spring will appear when you right-click.
You can see the value of the movement at this time.
Then enter the distance you want to move.
Click OK.
In the same way, it is also possible to place and move the shape line.
For example, we want to lengthen this skirt.
We choose the move shape line tool.
Select the edge of the skirt and drag it down.
At the same time, click on the right button.
Enter the value.
Then modify it.
In the same way, at the time of shortening,
we put the skirt up and then right-click.
At this time, you can see that the value in the window is negative.
Because at this time this plate is shortening,
so the value is negative.
Then we also have to enter the value when entering.
We use this negative to shorten this plate.
Finally, we use the move shape line tool.
This tool also needs to pay attention to the number when entering the value.
But the difference is that even if we look at it,
we are shrinking this plate.
But its number shows the correct value.
So when entering the value,
we must pay attention.
When shrinking the plate, enter the negative value.
When enlarging the plate, enter the correct value.
Next is the improvement of 3D sewing line.
In the appearance of some thick-fitting clothing-style sewing lines,
due to the different direction of the direction of the underlying sewing volume,
it will lead to the effect of the clothing on the sewing line
showing different thickness on both sides.
Then we can use this optimization function
to show it.
Using the sewing line effect of this V-shape on the sleeve,
we use the editing sewing line tool
to select the sewing line of this circle.
In the element weapon,
we find the 3D sewing line.
The default is the seam.
The seam effect cannot reflect the thickness of the two sides.
The thickness is different.
So we need to change the seam to the seam.
The seam is the seam of the sleeve.
After the change,
you can see that the effect of this sewing line
is displayed on this side.
You can see that the default is the effect of the sewing line
displayed on seam A.
If you switch to seam B,
that is the effect of the sewing line displayed on this side.
Now you can see the difference in thickness clearly.
In fact, this is all through the effect of the sewing line.
The effect of the sewing line can be displayed.
We can enter different strength and thickness
to show different effects.
And this effect is also symmetrical.
I need to explain that
seam A is the seam of the sewing line
added for the first time when sewing the sewing line.
Seam B is the second seam.
If you correct the seam like this,
you can end up with the inner seam
and seam B on the outer seam.
If you correct the seam like this,
seam A will not have a seam as before.
You will have a seam as before.
You must also fix this seam on your part.
And this way,
you will have the seam.
The next thing that I will explain
are side seam.
Select the editor, and click on Sample Board.
You can see that the lower right corner of the window can be switched to a 3D window,
and the three windows can be displayed at the same time.
Let's show it at the same time.
In 7.1, when we modify the parameters in 7.1,
we can make a real-time preview of the version in the 2D window.
This is a new function that we have added.
Now I will modify the width of the front panel to 180 mm.
In the 2D window, you can see a real-time change in the width of the front panel.
Then modify the width of the whole shoulder.
And the width of the front panel.
Then modify the width of the back panel.
Then click on Create.
In the 2D window, left-click to create a new version.
In the 3D window, you can see that
the parameterized version we just created
is automatically arranged on the model.
And it has been automatically modified.
This is also a new function that we have added in 7.1.
And you can see that in the upper right corner of the window,
we have added the Save and Load buttons,
and we have added the function to import and export parameters.
Let's click Save.
Select the Save path.
Then enter the file name.
You can save the data file in CSV format.
You can open and edit it using Excel.
Here you can modify the data.
For example, we will modify the length of the front panel to 75 mm.
After saving, click on the Load button.
You can load the data in.
You can see a change in our data.
Next, I will explain the optimization of the code.
There are three optimization points in total.
The first one is to increase the size of the virtual model,
AVS.
The second one is to display the code information of the file in the attribute editor.
The third one is to edit the code.
There are three tools, you can choose which one to edit.
First, let's take a look at the first optimization.
Increase the size of the virtual model,
AVS.
In the previous version,
if you want to load the code of the virtual model,
we need to save the code of the virtual model
into an AVT file,
and then import it.
The current new functions can be more convenient
to modify the size of the virtual model.
First, let's go to the object window.
Click on the code.
Then click on Match Virtual Model.
Click on Update.
You can see that
it is not yet in the state of matching the code of the virtual model.
We will now switch the costume code number to M.
Then click on the Match 3D model button on the right.
Choose to increase the size of the virtual model.
We need to go to the library window
to copy the path of the code.
Let's close the window first.
Open the code in the library window.
Copy the path of the code.
Then repeat the same steps.
Select the AVS file of the code you need.
We match a virtual model to M.
Click on Open.
You can change the size of the model.
Click on OK.
Then click on Automatic wearing.
The costume of M is wearing
the model of M.
The L code is also the same operation.
Click on Match 3D model.
Click on Increase virtual model size.
We match a 14-digit model to the L code.
We also choose to change the size of the model.
Now our model M is matched to the model of M.
Let me talk about the second function of this code.
When we select the code,
We can see the code information of the code in the folder.
This is the name of the code group.
Click on the triangle to switch the code.
We can switch the different code.
Next, let's talk about the third application.
We use the editor to code one tool.
In the original application, we can only choose one number to edit.
Now we can click on the Shift key to edit multiple numbers at the same time.
Next, I will explain the third application.
Let's talk about the third application.
We can use the editor to edit multiple numbers at the same time.
Next, we can use the editor to edit multiple numbers at the same time.
In order to make the code easier, we will use the edit tool.
One is the edit tool.
The other is the edit tool which can edit the outline of the page.
Now, let's add a new code.
Since the POM algorithm has been optimized, the POM measurement line is no longer displayed in the new version, so there will be a double hint like this.
We click OK.
Let's go to the object window.
You can see that the previous POM will still have a name, but the data is gone.
The clothing is also blank.
Now let's re-measure the clothing length.
We select the measurement point in the object window and select the front length.
Then use the measurement tool to measure it.
After the measurement is complete,
you can see the measurement line in the object window.
You can see the measurement data in the object window.
Since the measurement point has been optimized and the measurement of the hole has been eliminated,
you can directly cross the gap in the middle of the plate when you select the measurement point.
Now let's measure the waist of this POM.
You can see that this POM has a waist.
We use the measurement point tool to measure the waist of the clothing circle.
The distance of the throat is automatically eliminated.
Then we can measure the waist.
In this way, the aging part of the clothing circle will be increased.
Next step is the improvement measurement of POM.
We use the measurement tool to measure the measurement line.
To check out the measurement line,
we need to check out the measurement line.
If you use the on-screen button,
you can check out the measurement line.
When we edit the outline, the measured line will also change along this line section,
and you can click the Shift key to do more selection.
Now let's select the outline, and right-click to select it as the measured point.
In addition to using the edit tool to directly select it as the measured point,
we can also use the measured point tool itself.
Now let's switch to the measured point tool.
Let's measure the length of the outline.
We click to select its starting point and end point.
Currently, it is a straight line.
Then use the edit measurement tool.
Right-click to select the type of outline length.
The outline will be displayed in yellow.
If you want to reverse the selection, right-click to select the effect.
Then click the opposite line section.
This is for the measurement of the outline of our outline.
You can also choose the measurement point to the X-axis or Y-axis.
Right-click to select the length of the X-axis or the length of the outline.
Let's look at the 2D model.
In the 2D function section, there are a few updates that have been optimized.
The first is the split curve function.
This function allows you to more accurately edit the location of the curve.
It has optimized the way to increase the curve point.
In the past, you could only add it to any position.
Now you can add the curve point according to the selected option in the entire section.
Let's use the edit curve tool.
For example, we use this ruler.
Press the right button to divide the line section.
The split curve option is the same as the plus point division option.
We choose the average section.
The number is 3.
Click OK.
We will add the first curve point.
The line is 2mm down.
This makes the curve of the ruler more natural.
I will introduce the optimization of the cross-border line.
This function is convenient for us to use in CLOUD.
Click OK.
to use the inner line in the cloud to make modifications and separations.
For example, I want to make a use of the scene of drawing a pocket.
For example, I want to make a separation design on the skirt.
This is an inner line I drew in advance.
In the previous version, if you want to make a similar separation,
you need to copy the inner line to the back.
And it is difficult to ensure accuracy.
Now you can directly separate the inner pattern across the seam line.
We now use the adjustment panel tool.
Right-click and select the seam line separation.
Separate the inner line.
The inner line on the other side will appear in the back according to the seam relationship.
Next, right-click and select the seam line separation.
Then, apply the fabric to the inner line.
This separation design is done very quickly.
Next, I will show you another advantage.
Change the length and edit the continuous multiple lines.
Let's use the pop-up sleeve of this dress.
In the previous version, you can only choose one line.
Right-click to change the length.
Now you can press the Shift key.
Select the continuous multiple lines.
Right-click to change the length.
Now we will change the length of the sleeve to 400 mm.
And you can choose the direction to change the length.
You can select the length divider type.
Then, press the Shift key.
With that, your cut of this
texture is complete.
Next, you can change the width.
Next, my colleague Amelia will introduce the content of the second half.
Hello, everyone.
Next, I will introduce the content of the second half.
The main updates related to virtual models.
This update includes editing virtual model measurements,
moving the measurement line by dragging the measurement point,
adding model configuration types, earrings and glasses,
and the model's hand position can be used separately.
Using the editing measurement virtual model tool in the 3D window,
you can see that there is a measurement line between the model's waist.
This line is horizontal, but in actual wear,
the back waist of the pants will be slightly higher than the front waist.
We can raise the measurement point of the back waist.
The mouse and the circle stop at the point in the back.
The left arrow drags it to move the measurement line.
Note that the measurement line will disappear after editing.
Switch the tool to the virtual model measurement.
Add the attachment.
Modify it again.
Next, I will teach you step by step how to add self-defined glasses and earrings.
Let's open the earring file first.
Here, the earring position is adjusted.
In the FBX file,
name the file as earring.
There are several options to pay attention to.
Choose a single target.
Hold.
The ratio is centimeters.
For the text, choose to sign in the media.
For other options, just follow the selection here.
Click OK.
Open a new project.
Open the FBX file saved just now
as a virtual model.
The unit number is still centimeters.
Just follow the selection here.
After opening it,
we find Merge here at the object window.
The last line of Merge is the object name.
Change the object name to earring.
After editing, save it.
It's still FBX.
Then, cover the original file.
Click OK.
Here, we need to look at the option settings.
In the first line here,
we need to choose to remove the skeleton.
Then, select a single target to merge.
The following unit is still centimeters.
The ratio is still 100% unchanged.
For the text, choose to sign in the media.
For other options,
just follow the selection here.
After the FBX file of the earring is processed,
the next step is to register it on the model.
Let's open the model first.
In the menu bar,
in the virtual model,
make a custom configuration.
Select the earring.
Enter the file of the earring.
The custom image must be prepared in advance.
Make it as a virtual image.
Select to generate.
The file is also named earring.
Because the FBX file cannot save the material type,
so the earring file we saved is still white.
After opening it,
we select it.
Then, change the material type to metal.
Then, save it again.
Cover the original file.
Here, select the earring.
Then, add the custom image.
Here, we delete the original configuration.
Then, open the new earring.
Let's see the effect.
The eyes and the earring are the same.
Here, we will demonstrate
how to modify the material name of the glasses.
Open a new project.
Then, open the material name of the glasses.
As a virtual model, open it.
Also, use the limit unit.
Then, in the material window,
we find the previous line of Merge.
Change its material name to Glasses.
Then, save it.
Here, we can see that
the process of making the earring and the glasses
has been summarized.
In the previous process,
there are more options to open and close.
But in fact, the whole process is divided into three steps.
First of all,
export the configuration file to the FBX file.
Then, open the FBX file.
Then, modify its material name.
Then, save it.
Then, open the model.
Make a custom configuration.
There are only three steps to make the glasses.
Then, when making the earring,
we made one more step.
We need to modify its material type.
In the new version,
you can use the virtual model's guard position separately.
For example,
we can use the virtual model to match the bag.
Change the position of the bag.
You can see the picture of POS1 and POS2 in the folder.
We can change the model to the position of POS2.
But the model's left hand uses the position of POS1.
Go back to the software.
We import the position of POS2 into it.
In some positions,
open it.
You can see the image of the whole body,
hands, left hand and right hand.
Here, we choose the whole body.
After changing the position,
we still need to modify it.
Then, import the position of POS1.
Use the left hand separately.
In this way,
the model's position will be modified.
Finally,
we add the bag.
Choose to keep the current size and position.
In addition,
the guard position can be stored separately.
In the other place,
choose the guard position.
Keep both hands in this file.
In this way,
you can save both hands in this file.
The hand position file can be applied to other positions.
You can choose both hands,
left hand or right hand.
And the window of the drawing room.
Here, the virtual model.
In the virtual model file,
an hand pose file is added.
There are four hand positions.
When showing some style,
for example, a vest will remove the arm of the platform.
In the new version,
we can counter-activate a part of the model,
such as the arm of the counter-activating model.
Use the move tool to choose a move in the 3D window.
Right-click the counter-activate virtual model on the model's arm.
You can see the model's arm has turned into a blue semi-transparent state.
It must have been counter-activated.
To pull it out.
Right-click to hide the anti-election.
This is a part of the model that can be hidden by the anti-election.
Next, we will hide the model and simulate it.
You can see that the suit sleeves are naturally pulled down.
Because the anti-election operation of the model is different from the previous one,
I will demonstrate it to you.
Let's display the model first.
Then right-click on the model.
Select all surfaces.
Select the entire model.
Right-click again.
Select the anti-election virtual model.
The entire model is now anti-election.
Next, I will introduce the functional updates in the process.
In the new version, the sticker version made using the sticker tool can also participate in the material calculation.
Use the sticker tool.
Select all surfaces.
You can see that this style adds stickers to the position of the sleeves and the skirt.
Enter the print and print mode.
Change to the corresponding fabric.
You can see that three stickers are automatically generated here.
Here I arrange them in advance on the layout step.
The default sticker version is 45 degrees oblique.
If you need to change the direction of the stripping of the sticker version,
you can rotate the version directly.
You can rotate the version directly to modify it.
Or you can switch to the simulation mode.
After adding the sticker version,
In the attribute editor,
you can modify the direction of the stripping line.
For example, change the direction to the tail stripping.
After changing, enter the print mode.
You can see that the direction of the board has changed, and it is rearranged again.
Next, use another file to show the optimization of other functions in the process.
In the new version, in addition to the original shrinkage of the sewing line,
the stretch of the sewing line is also added.
For example, the only one here is the length and short side of the sewing box.
Here, it should be the short side based on the long side to add stretch.
Use the edit sewing line tool to select the sewing line.
Open the stretch and select stretch.
The strength default is 0.1, and the proportion default is 100%.
The strength, according to the material and style,
should be adjusted accordingly.
The greater the strength, the closer it will be to the predicted proportion.
Here we can adjust it to 1.
As for the proportion, when selecting stretch,
this 100% is the length of the long side.
When selecting shrinkage, it is 100% of the length of the short side.
In short,
when selecting the length of the long side and the short side of the long side,
the shrinkage fabric is selected to shrink,
and the stitch fabric is selected to stretch.
Let's go back to the software and simulate it.
Let's take a look at the results.
You can see that the gap is a little wider,
which is closer to the real sewing box effect.
Let's take a look at the results.
The new feature has optimized the performance of the sewing line on the sewing line.
You can see the sewing line of the pants here.
Because the width is relatively large,
there are cracks in the place where the sewing line is attached.
Using the edit sewing line tool,
we select this sewing line.
Then here in the mouse editor,
open the flattening function.
It can be optimized.
It can improve this problem.
In order to make a more three-dimensional and diversified sewing line effect,
we can now make a self-defined OBJ sewing line.
We can use this function to add a letter-sculpting effect
to the front chest position of this style.
See the front chest here.
In the object window page,
we add a new sewing line.
The sewing line will be added.
In the middle of the sewing line,
there is a plus button on the right side of the type.
If you click it,
a new OBJ sewing line will appear.
Here I will introduce you the settings for the sewing line.
The left side is the parameter settings.
The right side is the window of the effect preview.
First, look at the information on the left.
The default unit is mm.
It is also customized according to the size of the OBJ.
to modify the size of the OBJ file.
If you need to change the direction of the OBJ file,
just select this change in the appropriate position.
The bottom shows the length and width of the OBJ model.
When we import this OBJ file,
the length and width will automatically be displayed.
The center refers to the distance between OBJs.
At the same time, the obvious effects that we set
can be previewed in the window on the right.
Use the wheel to slide it down.
Here, we import the OBJ file into the OBJ name line.
Use the default millimeter.
The diameter does not need to be modified.
Click Confirm.
Add the name line to the internal line.
Here, we can use the free name line.
Once the entire inner line of the frame is selected,
add the self-defined name line.
We can open the 3D window to display the inner line.
To confirm the effect of the name line.
The double rowing star here will do a good job.
Select that line at the window on the object,
First, change the diameter to 1 1⁸ and then scroll down to find the number of lines.
Change the number of lines to 2 and change the diameter to 1⁴.
This effect is better.
Change the material type of OBJ to gemstone.
You can choose a color you like. I choose white here.
Open the rendering window.
You can see the effect of the calculation.
When we use the sticker function to show the hardening effect such as heat transfer, digital spray, and ink ink,
in order to show the sharpness of the original lower layer of the plant,
it will give the sticker plus the發現 picture of the plant,
but the previous version could not adjust the size of the發現 picture.
You can adjust it in the new version.
We choose this sticker.
You can see that it is already added here.
This is the發現 picture.
This sticker is at the back of the V1.
We can see the 8-angle.
The sticker also adds the發現 picture of the plant.
We can see that the ratio of the發現 picture of the sticker to the發現 picture of the plant is not small.
The ratio of the發現 picture of the sticker is 100%.
The ratio of the發現 picture of the sticker to the發現 picture of the plant is 300%.
Let's take a look at the發現 picture of the large-bonded plant.
Its ratio is 50%.
We can change the proportion of the sticking picture to the發現 picture to 50%.
After the change, we see the 3D window.
to match the size of the discovery map of the plant.
The 7.1 version has updated some rendering settings.
Let's go to the rendering window.
The update this time focuses on the light attribute.
In the attribute editor, we can see the new preview of the light.
Scroll down to the list.
There are several light previews to choose from.
Stop the mouse.
A preview will appear on the option.
Click on the light setting you want.
You can see that the corresponding light appears in the editor.
On the left side of the light, the corresponding light icon will now be displayed.
You can show the type of light more clearly.
On the right side of the light, three small buttons have been added.
The first is to activate and close the light.
The second is to turn off the light.
ную
The third one is shown in rendering.
In this way, you can separate and set the lighting to be displayed and hidden in the 3D window and the rendering window.
It's good for us to run this in the rendering window.
Finally, if you want to go back to the default lighting settings,
just click Reset in the upper right corner.
You can switch back to the default lighting.
The function of the text editor has also been optimized and updated.
Next, let's look at the fabric of the skirt.
Go to the object window and select the fabric of the skirt.
In the text editor, open the text editor page.
Then click the Add button on the left.
Enter the AR file of the draft.
This draft has a total of three layers.
Select the layer to be entered.
You can enter these three layers separately.
We select all three layers.
Select the drawing board.
This is to merge these three layers together as a complete picture.
Enter.
Here we select the layer to be entered.
Click OK.
After entering, you can see that there are four layers in the lower left corner.
The lowest layer is the original plant texture.
Select any flower pattern.
The size of the line frame is the size of the picture.
These three flower patterns are the same size.
The yellow high-light line frame is the size of the fabric,
that is, the size of a circle.
Now we want to use the size of the flower pattern to make a circle.
Select any flower pattern.
Right click.
Make the size of the fabric suitable for the selected image.
Select any picture.
Now it's being circled by the size of the flower pattern.
Make the size of the flower pattern form a circle.
Let's zoom in to see the details.
After hiding the three-layer flower pattern,
you will find that the bottom layer is too small.
To hide the bottom layer,
you need to open the flat plate at the bottom of the repeat.
You need to open the flat plate at the bottom of the repeat.
As you can see, we can select multiple layers at once.
Press Ctrl and select the three-layer flower pattern.
Change it to a flat bottom.
This will show the texture of the food.
Open the layer and change the mixture to a flat bottom.
Check the effect.
Next, I'll show you some other new features.
The new group function can be used to group plants.
There are more plants in this model.
We can group plants in the same way as clothes.
On the top left corner, click on the Create a new file folder button.
Click on Create a new file folder.
Name it as下装.
On the left side of the original group, there is a small pen.
Click on the name as上装.
We can drag the plant used for the pants to the next group.
You can also press Shift to select more plants and drag them at once.
Drag is a moving plant.
On any plant, right-click and you can see that drag is used to move.
You can also click on it.
Click on Drag to copy.
If you change to Drag to copy,
Drag will copy the plant to another group.
For example, this yellow plant.
You can drag it to the next group.
When we drag it to the next group,
the plant will be copied.
The plant here is copied to the next group.
In fact, the two plants are still in the same fabric.
On the right side of the group,
we can drag the plant to the next group.
On the right, we have the button to add and open the material.
These two buttons can be used to load the material.
On the right, we have the button to delete the folder.
In the new version,
to make it easier for users to change the color of various materials,
we have updated the color window as well.
Let's open the color window.
Under the window, we can see that the original confirmation cancel
has now become the complete application cancel.
After selecting a color, we click on the application in the middle
to use the color.
At this point, we can directly select another material,
then select another color and apply it.
In other words, the color window can be opened all the time.
When the window is opened, we can try to control it.
After changing all the colors,
we click on the window to complete it.
We can now turn off the color window.
The color window has also been updated.
There are more material for this type of material.
If you want to change the color of the drawstring,
you need to scroll down to find the color window.
We see that there is a small arrow on the left side of the material.
Click on it to close the material group.
It only shows the first material.
The small arrow will go down.
Click again to open it.
In addition to the material name line, you can also close it.
There is also a pull-up at the bottom.
After closing all of these, you can see the attached information directly.
Click on it to close it.
After opening the display version name in the 2D window,
the version with the button will no longer display the name of the button.
You can see the name of the version more clearly.
Click on the button to close the window.
Finally, we see the update of the animation mode.
The left side is version 7.0 and the right side is version 7.1.
Click on the button to close the window.
The text in the text box has disappeared.
There is more space for operation.
The bottom has new settings for the number of frames.
Let's zoom in on the 7.1 interface.
The number of frames can be from minus 10,000 to the maximum of 10,000.
Click on the button to close the window.
copying the column with the frame several times.
side maison200
Japan's reward modules can be slower than the others.
The number of frames can be changed depending on the armas.
eleven to twelve
and the button to the next frame
can be easily moved around
and can be easily edited into the animation.
That's all for the new features of version 7.1.
Thank you.